Guide to the C-SPAN records, 1809, 1978-2012
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center
- Series 10: Audiovisual (Boxes 445-452), 1980s-2012
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-Carolyn Chambers-Panasonic DAT 44.1 kHz, November 18, 1998 (Box 447)
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-Allan Block-Panasonic DAT 44.1 kHz, February 4, 1999 (Box 447)
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-Leo Hindert-Panasonic DAT 48 kHz, November 19, 1997 (Box 447)
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-Gerry Lenfest-Panasonic DAT, circa 1998 (Box 447)
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-Marvin Jones-Panasonic DAT Master, Mono, 48 kHz, November 18, 1997 (Box 447)
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-John Rigas-Panasonic DAT, April 13, 1998 (Box 447)
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-Jeff Bennis-Panasonic DAT 48 kHz, November 18, 1997 (Box 448)
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-Tom Might-Panasonic DAT Master, 44.1 kHz, November 13, 1997 (Box 448)
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-Frank Schurz-Panasonic DAT 44.1 kHz, October 13, 1998 (Box 448)
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-Jim Robbins-Panasonic DAT, circa 1998 (Box 448)
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-Michael Willner-Panasonic DAT Master, January 21, 1998 (Box 448)
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-Jack Frazee-Panasonic DAT Master, 44.1 kHz, October 26, 198 (Box 448)
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-Tom Waldrop-Panasonic DAT 44.1 kHz, March 20, 1998 (Box 448)
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-Dick Green-Cassette Tape, circa 1990s (Box 448)
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-Amos Hostetter-Cassette Tape, circa 1990s (Box 448)
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-Jack Frazee-Cassette Tape, circa 1990s (Box 448)
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-Barry Babcock-Cassette Tape, circa 1990s (Box 448)
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-Bob Miron-Cassette Tape, circa 1990s (Box 448)
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-Marvin Jones-Master Dub-Cassette Tape, circa 1990s (Box 448)
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-Marvin Jones-Cassette Tape, circa 1990s (Box 448)
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-Bill Stewart-Cassette Tape, circa 1990s (Box 448)
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-Tom Might-Cassette Tape, November 1997 (Box 448)
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-Jack Poitle-Cassette Tape, November 18, 1997 (Box 448)
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-Jack Poitle-Master Dub-Cassette Tape, November 18, 1997 (Box 448)
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-Fred Nichols-Cassette Tape, circa 1990s (Box 448)
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-Marvin Jones-Cassette Tape, November 18, 1997 (Box 448)
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-Sheila Mahoney-Cassette Tape, circa 1990s (Box 448)
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-Sheila Mahoney-Cassette Tape, circa 1990s (Box 448)
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-Jim Whitson-Cassette Tape, circa 1990s (Box 448)
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-Jeff Bennis-Master Dub A Side-Cassette Tape, circa 1990s (Box 448)
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-Jeff Bennis-Master Dub B Side-Cassette Tape, circa 1990s (Box 448)
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-Jeff Bennis-Cassette Tape, circa 1990s (Box 448)
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-Jeff Marcus-Cassette Tape, circa 1990s (Box 448)
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-Michall Willner-Cassette Tape, circa 1990s (Box 448)
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-Bill Brisman-Cassette Tape, circa 1990s (Box 448)
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-Allan Block-Tape 2-Cassette Tape, circa 1990s (Box 448)
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-Tom Might-Cable One-Cassette Tape, November 13, 1997 (Box 448)
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-Jim Robbins-Cassette Tape, circa 1990s (Box 448)
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-John Rigas-Cassette Tape, circa 1990s (Box 448)
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-Bill Busman-Cassette Tape, circa 1990s (Box 448)
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-John Evans-Cassette Tape, circa 1990s (Box 448)
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-Jan Peters-Cassette Tape, circa 1990s (Box 448)
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-Mike Burrus-Cassette Tape, circa 1990s (Box 448)
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-Tom Waldrop-Cassette Tape, circa 1990s (Box 448)
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-Jerry Lindaver-Tape 1-Cassette Tape, circa 1990s (Box 448)
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-Jerry Lindaver-Tape 2-Cassette Tape, circa 1990s (Box 448)
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-Jeff Marcus-Cassette Tape, circa 1990s (Box 448)
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-Jeff Bennis-Cassette Tape, circa 1990s (Box 448)
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-Carolyn Chambers-Cassette Tape, circa 1990s (Box 448)
  - C-SPAN Board Member Interview-David McCourt-Cassette Tape, circa 1990s (Box 448)
  - "John R. Baby Chicks"-Cassette Tape, circa 1980s (Box 448)
  - Floppy Disk-Content Unknown, circa 1990s (Box 449)
  - Floppy Disk-Content Unknown, circa 1990s (Box 449)
  - "Must2.bmp-Must have headlines"-Floppy Disk, circa 1990s (Box 449)
  - "Tocqueville poster header"-Floppy Disk, circa 1990s (Box 449)
  - "Quotes 2 (not formatted)"-Floppy Disk, circa 1990s (Box 449)
  - "More C-SPAN Logos-Washington Journal, C-SPAN.org, Booknotes, C-SPAN School Bus"-Floppy Disk, circa 1990s (Box 449)
  - Various Documents-Floppy Disk, circa 1990s (Box 449)
  - "Must have headlines"-Floppy Disk, circa 1990s (Box 449)
  - "Alternate Headlines"-Floppy Disk, circa 1990s (Box 449)
  - "C-SPAN Logos-American Presidents-C-SPAN in clsrm-C-SPAN-C-SPAN2-C-SPAN Extra-Radio 90-Booknotes-Book TV"-Floppy Disk, circa 1990s (Box 449)
  - "Board Minutes'-Floppy Disk, circa 1990s (Box 449)
  - "Board Newsletter and Special Project"-Floppy Disk, circa 1990s (Box 449)
  - "C-SPAN Bus Logo"-Floppy Disk, circa 1990s (Box 449)
  - "Table of Contents-Credits (photo)-Cable Acknowledgments (Revision 3/2)-Note on Sources"-Floppy Disk, circa 1990s (Box 449)
  - "TOC/C-SPAN Bus"-Floppy Disk, circa 1990s (Box 449)
  - Floppy Disk-Content Unknown, circa 1990s (Box 449)
  - Floppy Disk-Content Unknown, circa 1990s (Box 449)
  - Floppy Disk-Content Unknown, circa 1990s (Box 449)
  - Floppy Disk-Content Unknown, circa 1990s (Box 449)
  - "Theresa's Gen[eral] Corr[espondence]"-Floppy Disk, February 8, 1994 (Box 449)
  - "Susan's Disk"-Floppy Disk, February 8, 1994 (Box 449)
  - "Phone List-Bruce"-Floppy Disk, May 1994 (Box 449)
  - "Rob's Disk"-Floppy Disk, February 8, 1994 (Box 449)
  - "C-SPAN/DirecTV Affiliation Agreement"-Floppy Disk, circa 2000s (Box 449)
  - "Bruce Collins, Esq."-Floppy Disk, circa 2000s (Box 449)
  - "Tocqueville Project-Poster Art-hires-Property of C-SPAN"-Zip Drive, circa 1990s (Box 449)
  - "Archive: Radio launch photos-C-SPAN Radio 90 Launch Day"-Zip Drive, October 9, 1997 (Box 449)
  - "Cleveland 4"-Zip Drive, circa 1990s (Box 449)
  - "Tocqueville Cahier-Low Res-Property of C-SPAN"-Zip Drive, circa 1990s (Box 449)
  - "Images 2"-CD-ROM, circa 2000s (Box 449)
  - CD-ROM-Content Unknown, circa 2000s (Box 449)
  - CD-ROM-Content Unknown, circa 2000s (Box 449)
  - CD-ROM-Content Unknown, circa 2000s (Box 449)
  - "Images 1"-CD-ROM, circa 2000s (Box 449)
  - Kodak Picture CD-Unknown Content, circa 2000s (Box 449)
  - Brian Lamb Reception-Brian Lamb Interview with Mitch Daniels-CD-ROM, September 29, 2011 (Box 449)
  - C-SPAN-DVD-ROM-Two Copies, circa 2000s (Box 449)
  - "C3 Prime"-DVD-ROM, February 23, 2010 (Box 449)
  - CD-ROM-Content Unknown, circa 2000s (Box 449)
  - "10th Anniver[sary]"-Grand Traverse Regional Community Foundation-CD-ROM, circa 2000s (Box 449)
  - Conversations with People at the Leading Edge...Who Will You Trust?-Brian Lamb-CD, 1999 (Box 449)
  - "Backup Photos-C-SPAN"-CD-ROM, circa 2000 (Box 449)
  - "Meg Steele Website-CSiC-American Writers"-CD-ROM, February 5, 2002 (Box 449)
  - Bohan and Carroll Family Album-CD-ROM, circa 1990s (Box 449)
  - "Brian Lamb Photos"-CD-ROM, circa 1990s (Box 449)
  - "Focus Part 2"-C-SPAN DVD, 2006 (Box 449)
  - "Part 1"-C-SPAN DVD, 2006 (Box 449)
  - "The Lottery-TRT 80 min"-DVD-ROM, circa 1990s (Box 449)
  - "Scholarship"-Compudisk, circa 2000s (Box 449)
  - "C-SPAN"-5.25" Floppy Disk, October 6-October 19 1989 (Box 449)
  - 5.25" Floppy Disk-Content Unknown, September 22-October 5, 1989 (Box 449)
  - "From Apex 9/14/89-Lettercom Premiums-Count: 200"-5.25" Floppy Disk, September 8-21, 1989 (Box 449)
  - "From Apex 9/28/89-Lettercom Premiums-Count: 236"-5.25" Floppy Disk, August 25-September 7, 1989 (Box 449)
  - Update on Stata Files-5.25" Floppy Disk, circa 1980s (Box 449)
  - 5.25" Floppy Disk-Content Unknown, December 8, 1989 (Box 449)
  - "C-SPAN"-5.25" Floppy Disk, November 17-November 30, 1989 (Box 449)
  - "Reid late Nov."-5.25" Floppy Disk, November 3-November 16, 1989 (Box 449)
  - 5.25" Floppy Disk-Content Unknown, October 20, 1989 (Box 449)
  - "Ken Gunter"-Sony MC60 Microcassette, circa 1980s (Box 449)
  - "Bob Rosencrans-Las Vegas"-Sony MC60 Microcassette, May 19, 1989 (Box 449)
  - "Update Convention"-Scotchcart II, circa 1980s (Box 449)
  - "In: State Dept. Briefing"-Scotchcart II, circa 1980s (Box 449)
  - Tocqueville Quotes "Born Yesterday"-MII Videocassette, circa 1990s (Box 450)
  - Tocqueville Quotations Compilation-MII Videocassette, February 24, 1997 (Box 450)
  - Tocqueville Logo Design Ideas-MII Videocassette, October 22, 1996 (Box 450)
  - Tocqueville Quotations Compilation-MII Videocassette, February 18, 1997 (Box 450)
  - Tocqueville Quotes: Brian Lamb and Political Figures-MII Videocassette, circa 1990s (Box 450)
  - Dr. Splaine Training-Tocqueville-MII Videocassette, February 28, 1997 (Box 450)
  - Internal Workshop-Tocqueville-Dub-MII Videocassette, April 18, June 5, 1996 (Box 450)
  - "Plaque presentation-Return to J. Wheeler"-M20 Panasonic Video Cassette, circa 1990s (Box 450)
  - "Timothy's presentation at Colony House-Reception-Colony house-Tocq.-Newport, RI"-M20 Panasonic Video Cassette, circa 1990s (Box 450)
  - George Shea-"Attacks Plans-Persian Gulf War G. Shea"-VHS, circa 1990s (Box 450)
  - "The American Hour-George Shea"-VHS, circa 1990s (Box 450)
  - Tocqueville Clips-VHS, circa 1990s (Box 450)
  - Internal Workshop-Tocqueville-VHS, April 18, 1996 (Box 450)
  - Splaine-The Tocqueville Sessions 1 and 2-VHS, March 26, 1997 (Box 450)
  - Advanced Workshop Dinner-James Schleifer, Guest Speaker-"Schleifer's Speech"-VHS, circa 1990s (Box 450)
  - Internal Workshop-Tocqueville-VHS, April 18, 1996 (Box 450)
  - Tocqueville-Education Resources-"Teaching with Tocqueville"-VHS-Two Copies, November 11, 1997 (Box 450)
  - Campaign 96-Election Night-Road to the Capital-U-matic Videocassette, November 5, 1996 (Box 450)
  - Lincoln-Douglas Debates-U-matic Videocassette, circa 1990s (Box 450)
  - Rodrigue: A Man and His Dog-VHS, 1993 (Box 450)
  - Berlin-Journey of a City-VHS, 1995 (Box 450)
  - The Journey of a Butterfly-VHS, circa 1995 (Box 450)
  - "Cracker Barrell-'Path to Stardom-Mandy Barnett'"-VHS, August 23, 1995 (Box 450)
  - Borders, Inc.-Periodicals-VHS, circa 1990s (Box 450)
  - Perich and Partners-Borders Books, Music, and Cafe-VHS, December 17, 1996 (Box 450)
  - "Obstruction of Justice-'The Mena Connection'"-VHS, circa 1990s (Box 450)
  - Alfan Production-1996 Political Demonstration Reel-VHS (Box 450)
  - Grad-u-Vision Presents College of the Holy Cross-Class of 1996-VHS (Box 450)
  - "PCN Profiles Sen. Vincent Fumo-PA Journalists Year End Review"-VHS, December 18, 1996 (Box 450)
  - The Telecommunications and Information Revolution-VHS, circa 1990s (Box 450)
  - VHS-Content Unknown, circa 1990s (Box 450)
  - Advertisements-VHS, circa 1990s (Box 450)
  - Minister Louis Farrakhan-Documentary and Concert Performance-VHS, 1995 (Box 450)
  - "Indiana Historical Society 'Challenge for a New Century'"-VHS, November 25, 1996 (Box 450)
  - "A Gathering of Governors"-VHS, April 14, 1993 (Box 451)
  - "Deutsch/Dworin Inc.-Fiber Optics-Programming-Cable in the Classroom-Future Technology"-VHS, January 10, 1994 (Box 451)
  - "Pittsburgh Drug Legalization-4 Hours-David Nayberg"-VHS, January 21, 1994 (Box 451)
  - "Jerry"-VHS, circa 1990s (Box 451)
  - "Tom Henley-Restore the Republic"-VHS, circa 1990s (Box 451)
  - "Resurrection School-WWII Commemorative Exhibit w/ Daniel Ramsay and Patrick Delarosa-Pascagoula(?)-Ms."-VHS, May 1, 1994 (Box 451)
  - "PSA: C-SPAN and local cable operator-Presidential Timeline Give-away-30 second spot"-VHS, circa 1990s (Box 451)
  - "'Education Showcase'-October 1993-EduCable"-VHS (Box 451)
  - "PSA: C-SPAN and local cable operator-Presidential Timeline Give-away-30 second spot"-VHS, circa 1990s (Box 451)
  - "'Cable's Gift To America' Ad Campaign"-VHS, 1998 (Box 451)
  - "Shell Century Three Leaders: America's Best and Brightest-A scholarship program of the NASSP and Shell Oil Company"-VHS, 1990 (Box 451)
  - "PSA: C-SPAN and local cable operator-Presidential Timeline Give-away-30 second spot"-Betacam SP Videocassette, circa 1990s (Box 451)
  - "American Writers II Series Promo"-Betacam SP Videocassette, circa 1990s (Box 451)
  - "C-SPAN Board of Directors Meeting-1996 National Portrait Gallery/Richard Norton Smith and Doug Brinkley"-VHS (Box 451)
  - "News Segments-TeleCable-C-SPAN School Bus Tour"-VHS, January 11, 1994 (Box 451)
  - "Peter Hart"-VHS, circa 1990s (Box 451)
  - "'Broadcast Awards 1996'-TRT: 20:38"-VHS, June 26, 1996 (Box 451)
  - "Tom Might-Post-Newsweek-Wash[ington] J[our]n[a]l-'Texarkana'"-VHS, June 7, 1996 (Box 451)
  - C-SPAN VHS-Content Unknown, circa 1990s (Box 451)
  - "Jerry"-VHS, circa 1990s (Box 451)
  - "Hello DC, This is Pittsburgh (may we come in?)"-VHS, September 1995 (Box 451)
  - "Tape #1"-BCS-20 U-matic Videocassette, July 31, 1988 (Box 451)
  - "C-SPAN Seminar for Professors-Tape #3"-BCS-20 U-matic Videocassette, July 21, 1988 (Box 451)
  - "Tape #5-C-SPAN Seminar"-BCS-20 U-matic Videocassette, July 31, 1988 (Box 451)
  - "Tape #2"-BCS-20 U-matic Videocassette, July 31, 1988 (Box 451)
  - C-SPAN Promotional Tape-BCA-60 U-matic Videocassette, circa 1980s (Box 451)
  - "C-SPAN in the Classroom Seminars"-BCA-60 U-matic videocassette, January 15, 1989 (Box 451)
  - "Bruce Collins-C-SPAN in the Classroom-Program Length: 12:32-Air"-BCA-60 U-matic Videocassette, July 15, 1987 (Box 452)
  - "C-SPAN Professors' Seminar-Tape #2-VTR: CC"-BCA-60 U-matic Videocassette, July 21, 1987 (Box 452)
  - "#2-C-SPAN in the Classroom Seminar"-BCA-60 U-matic Videocassette, March 23, 1987 (Box 452)
  - "#1-C-SPAN in the Classroom Seminar-Closer you think about something you said was the uniqueness of C-SPAN"-BCA-60 U-matic Videocassette, March 23, 1987 (Box 452)
  - "Booknotes" Audiobook-Volume 1-6-Cassette Tape, circa 1990s (Box 452)
  - "The Contenders"-C-SPAN Original Series DVD-Ross Perot, 2011 (Box 452)
  - "The Contenders"-C-SPAN Original Series DVD-Thomas E. Dewey, 2011 (Box 452)
  - "The Contenders"-C-SPAN Original Series DVD-Charles Evans Hughes, 2011 (Box 452)
  - Presidential Libraries-History Uncovered-Media Preview Clips-DVD-Two Copies, September 2007 (Box 452)
  - "The White House" Documentary 15 Minute Preview Clip-DVD, 2006 (Box 452)
  - "The Capitol" on C-SPAN Radio Media Tour w/ Mark Farkas-Disc 1-CD, June 29-July 6, 2006 (Box 452)
  - "The Capitol" on C-SPAN Radio Media Tour w/ Mark Farkas-Disc 2-CD, June 29-July 6, 2006 (Box 452)
  - "The Capitol" on C-SPAN Radio Media Tour w/ Mark Farkas-Disc 3-CD, June 29-July 6, 2006 (Box 452)
  - "Press Clips-RFK-C-SPAN Radio"-CD-ROM, circa 2000s (Box 452)
  - "Press Clips-RFK-C-SPAN Radio"-CD-ROM, circa 2000s (Box 452)
- Series 11: Memorabilia (Boxes 453-456), 1980s-2012
  This series includes memorabilia gathered from multiple C-SPAN functions and programs, such as the Tocqueville Tour, the Lincoln-Douglas Debates reenactment, the C-SPAN Bus, coverage of Presidential elections, in a variety of formats such as pens, pencils, pins, stickers, keychains, and many more.
  - C-SPAN Campaign 2012 Tote Bag (Box 453)
  - C-SPAN School Bus T-Shirt, circa 2000s (Box 453)
  - Tocqueville T-Shirt, circa 2000s (Box 453)
  - The Contenders Series T-Shirt, circa 2000s (Box 453)
  - C-SPAN 25 Years T-Shirt, circa 2004 (Box 453)
  - Lincoln-Douglas Debate T-Shirt, circa 2000s (Box 453)
  - American Presidents Series Presidential Fact Cards-Two Copies, circa 2000s (Box 453)
  - The Lincoln Douglas Debates Commemorative Notecards-Two Copies, circa 2000s (Box 453)
  - 96 Campaign Democratic National Convention Pass, 1996 (Box 453)
  - Bookmarks, Postcards, and Pamphlets, circa 1990s-2000s (Box 453)
  - US Congressional 1990 Directory-Viewer Guide (Box 454)
  - US Congressional 1993 Directory-Viewer Guide (Box 454)
  - US Congressional 1994 Directory-Viewer Guide (Box 454)
  - US Congressional 1995 Directory-Viewer Guide (Box 454)
  - US Congressional 1996 Directory-Viewer Guide (Box 454)
  - US Congressional 1997 Directory-Viewer Guide (Box 454)
  - US Congressional 1998 Directory-Viewer Guide (Box 454)
  - US Congressional 1999 Directory-Viewer Guide (Box 454)
  - US Congressional 2002 Directory-Viewer Guide (Box 454)
  - US Congressional 2007 Directory-Viewer Guide (Box 454)
  - C-SPAN Early Guide to Members of 105th Congress, 1996 (Box 454)
  - C-SPAN Early Guide to Members of 106th Congress, 1998 (Box 454)
  - Who's Covering Washington Guide, 1997 (Box 454)
  - C-SPAN Exploring the Capitol Guide-Two Copies, circa 2000s (Box 454)
  - C-SPAN Advertising Pamphlets, circa 2000s (Box 454)
  - Business Cards, circa 2000s (Box 454)
  - Common Sense-A Viewer's Guide to the British House of Commons, 1993 (Box 454)
  - Gavel to Gavel-A Guide to the Televised Proceedings of Congress-Two Copies, 1993 (Box 454)
  - America Goes to the Polls-1992 Election Calendar (Box 454)
  - U.S. Congress Handbook, 1992 (Box 454)
  - Booknotes Tote Bag, circa 1990s (Box 455)
  - BookTV Flash Clip, circa 1990s (Box 455)
  - Booknotes Fifth Anniversary Metal Bookmark, circa 1994 (Box 455)
  - Booknotes 10th Anniversary Metal Bookmark, circa 1999 (Box 455)
  - Booknotes-Brian P. Lamb-C-SPAN Air Date Sticker Roll, circa 1990s (Box 455)
  - C-SPAN Campaign 2000 Pin (Box 455)
  - C-SPAN American Writers Magnetic Poetry Set, circa 2000s (Box 455)
  - C-SPAN Campaign 2012 Pin (Box 455)
  - Lincoln-Douglas Debate Commemorative Rock, circa 1994 (Box 455)
  - Lincoln's Boyhood Home Commemorative Drinking Jar, circa 1995 (Box 455)
  - Abraham Lincoln's Coaster, circa 1996 (Box 455)
  - American Presidents and First Ladies Fact Cards, 2000 (Box 455)
  - C-SPAN3 Tote Bag, circa 2000s (Box 455)
  - C-SPAN NGA Annual Meeting, circa 2000s (Box 455)
  - Pizza, Beers, Bars, BookTV T-Shirt, circa 2000s (Box 455)
  - Signed "Clingore" Pillow, circa 1990s (Box 455)
  - C-SPAN American Writers Metal Bookmark, circa 1990s (Box 455)
  - C-SPAN Pins, Key Chains, Magnets, Pens, Paperweights, Watch, and Stickers, 1980s-1990s (Box 456)
- Series 12: Miscellaneous (Boxes 457-469, Map Cases 5.2 - 5.5), 1809-2012
  This series includes miscellaneous items such as award plaques gifted to C-SPAN and Brian Lamb from a number of organizations, newspapers, C-SPAN advertisements, loose scrapbook pages, framed pictures, exhibit panels of varying sizes, C-SPAN political cartoons, and an antique newspaper from 1809 given to Brian Lamb.
  - Golden Eagle Award to C-SPAN and Brian Lamb Plaque, 2001 (Box 457)
  - George Foster Peabody Award to C-SPAN Plaque, 1992 (Box 457)
  - University of Denver Official Printed and Matted "Thank You,", 2002-2003 (Box 457)
  - The Miller Center at University of Virginia "Thank You" Certificate to Brian Lamb, September 17, 2012 (Box 457)
  - Defense Information School Certificate of Appreciation to Brian Lamb, May 9, 2008 (Box 457)
  - Department of the Navy Award of Merit for Group Achievement to C-SPAN, January 23, 2003 (Box 457)
  - National Press Club President's Citation Award to Brian Lamb, July 24, 2012 (Box 457)
  - National Press Club Council of the Wisest Owls Award to Brian Lamb, 2008 (Box 457)
  - National Press Club Award to C-SPAN, 2004 (Box 457)
  - Commemorative Golden CableACE Award Winner-Coverage of the 1992 Presidential Election to C-SPAN (Box 457)
  - Brian Lamb's National Press Club Speech, December 6, 2004 (Box 457)
  - Lincoln Presenter of the Year Documents and Photos, February 1995 (Box 457)
  - C-SPAN Exhibit Panels, circa 1990s (Box 458)
  - C-SPAN Exhibit Panels, circa 1990s (Box 459)
  - C-SPAN Exhibit Panels, circa 1990s (Box 460)
  - C-SPAN School Bus Framed Tour Advertisement, circa 1990s (Box 461)
  - Framed Fake "B A Lamb Magazine" Cover, circa 1990s (Box 461)
  - Framed Picture of Brian Lamb and John Splaine in front of Lincoln-Douglas Debate Statue, circa 1990s (Box 461)
  - Daily News "C-SPAN(ing) the convention" Framed Article, circa 1992 (Box 461)
  - The New York Times "ABC and C-Span Attended Different Parties Together" Framed Article, circa 1992 (Box 461)
  - The Washington Times "Keating 5: Real-life drama on C-SPAN" Mounted Article, circa 1990s (Box 461)
  - Cable World-Marketing News "C-SPAN at 10: Challenges remain in gaining cable system distribution" Mounted Article, circa 1990s (Box 461)
  - Cable TV Business Commentary "Education Month" Mounted Article, circa 1990s (Box 461)
  - Los Angeles Times "For the Record, It's C-SPAN" Mounted Article, circa 1990s (Box 461)
  - The Washington Post "Man At Work" Mounted Article, circa 1990s (Box 461)
  - San Diego Union "Good interviews are Brian Lamb's style" Mounted Article, circa 1990s (Box 461)
  - Cable World "C-SPAN's Global Vision" Mounted Article, circa 1990s (Box 461)
  - The Guardian "Where voters tune in and talk back" Mounted Article, circa 1990s (Box 461)
  - Exhibit Panel, circa 1990s (Box 461)
  - Small Framed Drawing, circa 1990s (Box 461)
  - Scrapbook Entries, circa 1990s (Box 462)
  - Newspaper Negatives and C-SPAN Advertisements, circa 1990s (Box 463)
  - Newspapers, circa 1990s (Box 464)
  - Newspapers and Advertisements, circa 1990s (Box 465)
  - Local Newspapers, circa 1990s (Box 466)
  - Local Newspapers, circa 1990s (Box 467)
  - C-SPAN Political Cartoons, 1980s-1990s (Box 468)
  - Antique Newspaper Received by Brian Lamb in 2000, 1809 (Box 469)
  - Large Metal Letters Spelling Out "CSPAN,", circa 2000s (Box 470)
  - Booknotes Correspondence, 1998 - 2004 (Box 471, Folder 1)
  - C-SPAN Studio Block Diagram by Bob Hall, December 13, 1978 (Box 471, Folder 2)
  - MA-12XCTX Transmitter Instruction Manual, 1978 (Box 471, Folder 3)
  - C-SPAN Articles, 1996 - 2005 (Box 471, Folder 4)
  - On the Road to the White House with C-SPAN kit, circa 1995 (Box 471, Folder 5)
  - 96 Campaign Promotion Materials, 1996 (Box 471, Folder 6)
  - Photo of C-SPAN Bus in Front of Washington Monument, circa 1990 (Box 471, Folder 7)
  - C-SPAN School Bus Educator's Kit, circa 2000 (Box 471, Folder 8)
  - Cable in the Classroom Article, December 1993 (Box 471, Folder 9)
  - C-SPAN School Bus Photographs, circa 1990 (Box 471, Folder 10)
  - C-SPAN Blurbs and Correspondence, 1999 (Box 471, Folder 11)
  - Exhibit Panels and Framed Items, circa 1990s (Box Map Case 5.2)
  - Exhibit Panels and Framed Items, circa 1990s (Box Map Case 5.3)
  - Exhibit Panels and Framed Items, circa 1990s (Box Map Case 5.4)
  - Exhibit Panels and Framed Items, circa 1990s (Box Map Case 5.5)